Mathis Biabiany

Creative Technologist

Phone: +336 07 12 8479

Mail: mathis.biabiany@gmail.com

Portfolio: http://www.mathis-biabiany.fr

I'm a creative technologist based in Paris. I'm passionate about the realisation of interactive digital effects providing cool sensations to the user. I like to work on installations, physical projects or websites with a nice experience.

Experience:

Creative Technologist / Artist Freelance

October 2018 - Now

 Creative Developer at <u>Resn</u> (Amsterdam, Netherlands)

October 2016 - October 2018

• Web Developer at **Touaregs** (Paris, France)

October 2013 - June 2016

• Web Developer at La Vie du Rail (Paris, France)

Avril 2013 - July 2013

Technical Skills:

- HTML5/CSS3/Javascript
- WebGL / GLSL

Education:

 CRMA, in Interactive and Digital media communication programmes.

Gobelins, l'école de l'image, Paris, France. 2014 – 2016

Bachelor Web Development and Mobile.

Gennevilliers, France.

2013 - 2014

• DUT SRC, Network & Services of Communication.

Sarcelles, France.

2011 - 2013

BAC, in Sciences and Technologies of the Industry.

Saint-Denis, France.

2011

Awards:

- 2020: Darker Lights FWA SOTD
- 2020: Darker Lights AWWWARDS SOTD
- 2020: Darker Lights CSSDA SOTD
- 2019: L2D FWA SOTD
- 2019: L2D **CSSDA SOTD**
- 2019: Olivier Ouendeno FWA SOTD
- 2019: Olivier Ouendeno AWWWARDS SOTD
- 2019: Olivier Ouendeno CSSDA SOTD
- 2018: Mathis Biabiany FWA SOTD
- 2018: Mathis Biabiany AWWWARDS SOTD
- 2018: Mathis Biabiany CSSDA SOTD
- 2018: Célia Lopez FWA SOTD
- 2018: Célia Lopez AWWWARDS SOTD
- 2018: Célia Lopez CSSDA SOTD
- 2017: Resn Little Helper AWWWARDS SOTD
- 2017: Resn Little Helper FWA SOTM
- 2017: Christmas Experiment FWA SOTD
- 2017: DEVX Experiments AWWWARDS SOTD
- 2017: DEVX Experiments FWA SOTD
- 2017: DEVX Experiments CSSDA -SOTD

- 2017: Adidas Speedfactory AWWWARDS SOTD
- 2017: Adidas Speedfactory FWA SOTD
- 2017: Adidas Speedfactory CSSDA SOTM
- 2017: Adidas NMD AWWWARDS SOTD
- 2017: Adidas NMD FWA SOTD
- 2017: Adidas NMD CSSDA SOTD
- 2016: Christmas Experiment FWA SOTD
- 2016: HP Sound in Color AWWWARDS SOTD
- 2016: HP Sound in Color FWA SOTD
- 2016: HP Sound in Color CSSDA SOTD
- 2015: Gobelins interactive experiments **AWWWARDS SOTD**
- 2015: Gobelins interactive experiments **FWA SOTD**